FailWise Agent is a focused failure-aware AgentOps dashboard for resilient AI agents.
Most observability tools only show what happened. FailWise shows where the agent failed and why it matters.
It also shows recovery policy, confidence impact, and what operators should fix next.
Here is the default task: investigate why checkout errors increased in the last hour.
In the normal deterministic run, the graph stays green from planning to MCP, LLM, and final answer.
Now we simulate an MCP timeout. The MCP node fails, the diagnoser classifies it, and recovery uses trusted cache fallback.
The final answer is still useful, but confidence is downgraded because live context was unavailable.
Next is the live DeepSeek provider probe. If the provider fails, FailWise marks an LLM provider failure and routes to fallback.
Clicking any node shows input, output, latency, errors, diagnosis, and recovery action.
The full run log gives a timestamped trace of tool calls, failures, recovery policy, and confidence changes.
In a cache miss with no trusted context, FailWise refuses to invent an incident answer.
FailWise turns hidden agent failures into diagnosis, recovery, confidence impact, safe refusal, and operator remediation.